fragrancex.com 2011-05-14

# FragranceX.com - Security and Privacy

  | 

Security and Privacy

We are committed to your privacy and security. When you shop at FragranceX.com your security and privacy is 100% safe and guaranteed. 

Safety

All transactions are 100% safe and secure. Order details are encrypted with Secure Socket Layer (SSL) by Verisign, the industry standard. To verify our security with Verisign, simply click the logo to the right. 

Your Privacy

FragranceX.com Inc. respects your privacy and has established a privacy policy below for your information. Below is an explanation of what information we collect, why and how we use this information. Our privacy policy is part of the website www.fragranceX.com and governs your use of the website. The website is owned by FragranceX.com, Inc. All persons using this website or registering must be 18 years of age or older. 

FragranceX.com offers over 15,000 brand name fragrances, skincare and cosmetics. We are proud to offer brand names at discount prices with fast shipping worldwide. To process your order we need to retain your personal information to allow us and third parties to communicate with you. This information is used to process your orders and to provide you with discounts, promotions, personalization and to create the best user experience. 

Information We Collect

When you use FragranceX.com and any affiliated websites by placing an order, emailing us, joining a contest or promotion or registering with us, the information you provide is collected by us. FragranceX.com Inc. collects this information including your name, address, telephone number, email address, billing information and shipping information. Our server logs may also include information such as your Internet Protocol address, and the page you request. When you send email or other communications to FragranceX.com, we may retain those communications indefinitely or delete them. 

What are "cookies" and why do you need them enabled?

"Cookies" are small files placed on the hard drive of your computer which identifies you by a code or number. Most cookies are "session cookies", meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive once you sign out from FragranceX.com or close your web browser. We use cookies to keep track of items you place in your cart and to help process your order. In addition, cookies help to provide features and services such as allowing you to enter your password less frequently, remembering your preferences. 

Use of Information

FragranceX.com may use individual or aggregated information for any legally permissible purpose in FragranceX.com's sole discretion, including sharing your information with third parties that may use it to offer additional products and services to you. 

Corrections

If you would like to update or correct information you have provided to us, please email us at [_privacy@fragranceX.com_](mailto:privacy@fragranceX.com). 

Changes

FragranceX.com may update this policy at any time. We will post these changes so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it. By using FragranceX.com, Inc. after such changes and posting, you agree to be legally bound to abide by the changes and other provisions in the Privacy Policy. 

Mailing list preference

If you do not want to have your information shared with third parties, please email us at [_privacy@fragranceX.com_](mailto:privacy@fragranceX.com). Please include your name and address. If you unsubscribe from our promotional emails we will not share any information with any third parties. 

Information for persons residing outside the USA

Transfer of Personal Information outside the EEA. We process Personal Information in the United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process Personal Information on a server outside your own country. We use the highest encryption standards and best practices to protect your Personal Information. When you place an order with FragranceX.com, you consent to us transferring and hosting/storing your Personal information outside the EEA. 

Comments or Questions

Comments or Questions. If you have any questions or comments about this policy, please contact us at [_privacy@fragranceX.com_](mailto:privacy@fragranceX.com). 

Shop with confidence, we offer a 30 day money back guarantee. 

|
